Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES III. ACADEMIC PROGRAMS, (3 document boxes / 1.3 linear feet)
  The Academic Programs series consists of correspondence, newspaper clippings, and reports regarding academic programs administered by the college outside of the regular operations of academic departments. Those programs include the Ada Comstock Scholars Program, Honors Program, Junior Year Abroad, Bridge Program, Intermediate School 201, student exchanges, and several interdisciplinary programs.
  - Ada Comstock Scholars
    See Also Series XI. Events-Conferences-The Older Undergraduate Woman
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -General 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General 1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Jill Ker Conway Ada Comstock Scholars Supplemental Fund 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Studies (Box 1, Folder 8)
    See also Series III. Academic Programs-Student Exchange w/China -and- Series XIII. Graduate Work-American Studies Diploma Program-1975-1977
  - American Studies 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Studies 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Studies 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Program 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bridge Program 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Literature 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Comparative Literature 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Engineering Dual Degree 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Engineering Dual Degree 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hispanic Studies: (Box 2)
    See Series II. Academic Departments-Spanish and Portuguese. Not to be confused with Latin American Studies, an interdepartmental program which started after JKC's tenure.
  - History of Science 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Honors Program-Theses Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Honors and Independent Programs, Committee on1975-1976
  - Intermediate School 201 (I.S. 201) 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Studies 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Junior Year Abroad
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Study Abroad, Committee on
    - -General 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -General-Exchange Scholarships 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -England 1976-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Florence 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -France 1976-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -Geneva 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Hamburg 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Junior Year at Smith: (Box 3)
      See Series III. Academic Progs-Visiting Year at Smith
    - -Kyoto, Japan 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Spain-Cordoba 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Medieval Studies: (Box 3)
    See Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Medieval Studies Council
  - Peace and War Studies (Box 3, Folder 8)
    See also Series XIV. Intercollegiate Associations-Five Colleges-Academic Depts & Programs-Peace & World Security Studies1983-1985
  - Public Policy 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Student Exchange with China 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Student Exchange with China 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Student Exchange with Japan 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Visiting Year at Smith 1978- (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Visiting Year at Smith (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Women's Studies (Box 3, Folder 15)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Research Program on Women, Ad-hoc Committee to Design a 1979-1984
- SERIES IV. ADMINISTRATIVE ISSUES, (10 document boxes / 4.2 linear feet)
  This series documents activity in the President's Office which is either of a general nature, requiring the attention of only the president and her closest assistants, or requiring the participation of a number of administrative bodies at once. Included in this series are records relating to a number of general issues, such as Legislators and Legislation, Lesbianism, Race, and Women's Education. At the end of the series there is a collection of miscellaneous correspondence handled by the President's Office, filed in alphabetical order. Several issues, such as lesbianism, race and women's education, pervaded many areas of campus activity and were handled by several offices and departments. Because material on these topics can be found under a variety of headings, a Subject Guide has been provided on pages 9-12 of this finding aid to assist the researcher.
  - Administrative Structure 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Structure 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Calendar 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Calendar 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Energy Conservation 1977-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Coeducation: (Box 1)
    See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Women's Education
  - Fire Safety
    - -General 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -General 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Reports 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gilbreth, Lillian 1978-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Inclement Weather 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Legal Counsel 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Legal Counsel 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Legal Counsel 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Legal Counsel 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Legislation & Legislators
    See Also Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-AICUM -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-United States Government
    - -General 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -General 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -General 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Bipartisan Budget Appeal 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -Balanced Budget Amendment 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -Brademas Arts & Humanities Conference Hearings 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Copyright Law 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Education Appropriations Bill 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -Education Department Cabinet Level 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Equal Rights Amendment 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Faculty Retirement Mandates 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -Handicapped Access 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -Higher Education Act 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -National Endowment for the Humanities 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Standardized Testing 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Student Aid
      - -General 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - -General 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -General 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - -Draft Registration 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - -Massachusetts 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - -Massachusetts 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - -National Student Loan Reform Act 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - -Students in Health Professions 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - -Tuition Advance Fund 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - -Taxation
      - -General 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - -Charitable Gifts 1975, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -Credits for Parents 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -Faculty Housing 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Meals 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -Real Property 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - -Real Property 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - -Real Property-Whately 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - -Real Property-Whately 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - -Rental Properties: (Box 4)
        See Series V. Admin. Offices-Rental Properties
    - -Title IX (Box 4, Folder 10)
      See also Series IV. Administrative Issues-Legal Counsel -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Committee for the Concerns of Women in New England Colleges...1976-1979
    - -Women in Science Act 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lesbianism
    See Subject Guide for further sources of information
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Feminist & Lesbian Alumnae of Smith 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Workshops 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Media Coverage
    See also Series I. Biography-Publicity -and- Series V. Administrative Offices-Public Relations
    - -General (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Firing Line (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -New York Times (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Patent Policies & Procedures 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Posture Pictures 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Racism, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    See Subject Guide for further sources of information.
  - Research Questionnaires 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Research Questionnaires 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Research Questionnaires 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Research Questionnaires 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Research Questionnaires 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secondary Education (Box 6)
    - -General 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -Columbus School for Girls 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -Commonwealth School 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -Northfield-Mt. Hermon School 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -Phillips Academy [Andover] 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -Phillips Exeter Academy 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -Portsmouth Abbey 1980-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sexual Discrimination: (Box 6)
    See Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination
  - Sexual Harassment 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Smith College History (Box 6, Folder 12)
    See also Series XII. Faculty & Staff-Horowitz, Helen1975-1985
  - South Africa, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    See Subject Guide-Racism for further sources of information
  - Telecommunications (Box 7)
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -LAN [Local Area Network] 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Town & Gown Relations (Box 7)
    - -General 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -General 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -Academy of Music 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -Academy of Music 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -Autumn Inn 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -Clarke School for the Deaf (Box 7)
      See also Series XIII. Grad Work-Education & Child Study-Clarke School Teacher Training
      - -General 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - -General 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - -General (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - -Magna House 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -Correctional Facilities 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - -Daycare Facilities 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - -Hampshire Community Action Commission 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - -Hampshire County Business and Professional Women's Club 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - -Historical Projects and Groups 1975-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - -Hotel Northampton 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - -Nonotuck Savings Bank 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - -Northampton-Hatfield Scholarships: (Box 8)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Financial Aid-General
    - -Northampton Public Schools 1975-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - -Northampton State Hospital (Box 8, Folder 12)
      See also Series XIII. Graduate Work-School for Social Work-General, for correspondence regarding "60 Minutes" episode (5 OCT 1983), and correspondence regarding SSW internships at the hospital (8 JUL 1984 )1978-1981
    - -Northampton State Hospital 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - -Round Hill Club 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - -St. John's Episcopal Church: (Box 8)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Childcare Center at Sunnyside
    - -Skating Rink 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Tuition (Box 9)
    - -General 1975-1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -McPherson Report 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Wedgwood Commemorative China 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Women's Education (Box 9)
    See Subject Guide-Gender for further sources of information.
    - -General 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -General 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -Gender Study by Jeanne Block (Box 9)
      - -Correspondence 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - -Reports ca. 1977, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -"Effect of Coeducational Living on Radcliffe Women" 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Elizabeth Tidball 1979-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "Writing Papers: A Handbook for Students at Smith College" 1979-1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 10)
    - -A-B ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - -C-D ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - -E-H ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - -I-K ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - -L ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - -M ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - -N-Q ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - -R ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - -S ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - -T-V ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - -W-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- SERIES V. ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICES
  The files are arranged alphabetically by the most recent name of the office.
  Nearly nineteen document boxes (8 linear feet) of Development material is open for research. Due to the sensitive nature of the development process, however, there is a large collection of material which will be closed to researchers for a minimum of seventy-five years.
  The Administrative Offices series is the largest series in the Conway records. It includes correspondence and reports from individual offices as well as newspaper clippings and other general information about their activities and functions. Development comprises the largest section of the Administrative Offices series, specifically because fundraising became a much more significant part of the duties of the President during Conway's tenure than in previous administrations.
  There may also be useful information in the Buildings and Grounds series about the buildings in which the various offices were housed.
  - Academic Assistance, Center for 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Assistance in Written English, Committee for
  - Academic Computer Center 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    See Subject Guide-Computers, for further sources of information
  - Administrative Data Processing (Box 1)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Administrative Information Systems
  - Administrative Information Systems
    - -Annual Reports 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -General Jan-Mar 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -General Apr-Dec 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -General 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Dartmouth Visit Report 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Hammer Consultancy [on Data/Word Processing] 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Preliminary Report 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Final Report 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Implementation Committee 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Admissions (Box 2)
    See also Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Enrollment Mgmt Ctte -and- Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Admissions, Bd. of -and- Series IX. Cttes & Bds-Alumnae/Admissions Task Force -and- Series XV. Non-Smith Orgs-Cooperative Institutional Research Prog., for admissions statistics
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -General 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -General 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -General 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -General 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -General 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -General 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -General 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -General Jan-May 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -General Jun-Dec 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -General 1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Alumnae Candidates Committees 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Alumnae Candidates Committees 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Alumnae-Related Candidates 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Bassin Project to Improve Admissions
      - -General 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -General Jan-Apr 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - -General May-Dec 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - -General 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -Gene Reilly Group Reports 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -Workgroup Meeting 7-8 Jan 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Workgroup Meeting 18-19 Mar 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -Department Letters to Applicants 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -Minority Students
      - -General 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - -Statistics 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -National Merit Scholars 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - -Procedures Manual 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Southwest Strategy Organizer 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bookstore 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Bookstore Advisory Ctte
  - Business Manager
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - -Annual Reports 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - -Annual Reports 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -General 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Campus Safety (Box 5)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Security
  - Career Development Office
    - -Annual Reports 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -Annual Reports 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -Annual Reports 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -General 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - -General 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - -General 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - -General 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -General 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -General 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -General 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -General Jan-Aug 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -General Sep-Dec 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -General 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -Internships
      - -General 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - -Administrative Smith Interns 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - -Picker Washington Program 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -Organization and Operation Report 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -Statistics by Class 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -Statistics by Class 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -Summer Institute for Women in Higher Education 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Central Services 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chapel 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chapel 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chapel 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chapel 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chapel 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Child Care Center at Sunny Side 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Child Care Center at Sunny Side 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Controller 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Collection of Historic Clothing 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - College Relations (Box 8)
    See Series V. Administrative Offices-Public Relations
  - Dean of the College
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - -General 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - -General 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - -General Jan-Apr 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -General May-Dec 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -General 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - -General 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -Alcohol Policy 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Assistant to the Dean for Minority Affairs 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -Associate Dean for Student Activities 1978-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - -Associate Dean for Student Affairs 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - -Associate Dean for Student Affairs 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - -Associate Dean for Student Affairs 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - -Associate Dean for Student Affairs-Head Residents 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - -Associate Dean for Undergraduate Studies 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - -Class Deans 1976-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - -Class Deans 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - -College Handbook 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - -Orientation 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - -"A Plan for the Reorganization of the Office of the Dean..." 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - -Search for New Dean 1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dean of the Faculty
    - -General 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - -General 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - -General 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - -General 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - -General Jan-Jun 1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - -General Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - -General 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - -Administrative Processes and Information Flow 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - -Associate Dean 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Students
    - -General 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - -General 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - -Assistant Dean 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - -Assistant to the Dean for Minority Students 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Development
    - -General 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - -General 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - -General 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - -General 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - -General 1984-1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - -Acknowledgement Letters-Form Letters 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - -Agendas [for meetings with Development Staff] 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - -Agendas 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - -Alumnae Fund (Box 12)
      See Series VI. Alumnae-Alumnae Fund
    - -Brainstorming Sessions 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - -Bridge to the Eighties Volunteer Conference 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - -Capital Campaign
      - -General 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - -Cabinet Meetings 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - -Case Statement 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - -Conference 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - -Congratulatory Letters 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - -Openings 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - -Class Bequest Chairmen 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - -Consultants
      - -Gibson, E. Burr 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - -Goodale, Toni 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - -Marshall, Dorothy Nepper 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - -Pyle 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - -Coordinating Committee 1979-1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - -Corporate Brochure 1977, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - -Corporations
      - -General 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Development-Foundations-General
      - -Carnegie Corporation 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - -Chemical Bank 1975-1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - -Cheesebrough-Pond's 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - -Chevron 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - -CIGNA 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - -Citibank 1976-1985 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - -Citicorp 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - -Combustion Engineering, Inc. 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - -Connecticut Bank and Trust 1976, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - -Connecticut General Life 1978, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - -Conoco, Inc. 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - -Continental Group 1976-1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - -[Adolph] Coors Company 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - -Dow Chemical 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - -General Mills 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - -General Telephone and Electronics 1976-1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - -Honeywell 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - -IBM 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - -IBM 1980-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - -Kollmorgen Corporation 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - -Koppers Co. 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - -Merrill Lynch 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - -Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - -Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - -Norton Co. 1977-1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - -Perkin Elmer 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - -Philip Morris 1976-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - -Sun Refining and Marketing 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - -Texaco 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - -Texas Gulf 1976-1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - -Travelers Corporation 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - -Western Electric 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - -Miscellaneous Corporations, A-K ca. 1975-1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - -Miscellaneous Corporations, L-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - -Deferred Gifts and Bequests 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - -Deferred Gifts and Bequests 1977-1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - -Development Council 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - -Development Council-Advisory Board 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)